ABDERRAHIM NABAOUI

Agadir, Morocco • +212637852855 • nabaoui.abderrahim@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/abderrahimnabaoui

SUMMARY

Unity 3D Game Developer with over 8 years of experience. Proven ability to lead projects from concept to completion, develop hyper-casual games, and collaborate effectively with teams. Founder of Gamox, currently working as a freelancer developing hyper-casual games.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Unity Game Developer | Auto-Entrepreneur

Jan 2023 - Present (Morocco)

- Collaborated with clients to ensure game design met their requirements, achieving a 90% project success rate.
- Enhance game performance and user engagement by up to 40%.
- Developed and released more than 30 hyper-casual games.

Unity Game Developer | 9tales

Mar 2021 - Dec 2022 (France)

- Developed a demo NFT card game, transforming 100% of design specifications into a functional game.
- Enhanced game performance, leading to a 30% increase in player retention.
- Implemented 3D models and visual effects, enhancing game aesthetics by 60%.

CEO and Unity Game Developer | Gamox

Dec 2020 - Sep 2022 (Morocco)

- Led the development and release of 10 hyper-casual mobile games.
- Collaborate with 4 hyper-casual publisher studios, creating a game prototype to test it for achieving a hit game.

EDUCATION

1337 Coding School

Sep 2018 - Oct 2021

Information Technology Architect

- Specialized in computer graphics and game development.
- make a ray tracing rendering engine with C language, and small other games with Unity.

EWA School Oct 2013 - Oct 2015

Associate Degree in Web Development and Multimedia

• Learned algorithms, problem-solving, and web development (HTML/CSS, PHP).

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- **Technical Skills:** Unity 3D, C#, Game Design, 3D Modeling, Visual Effects (VFX), Problem Solving, Team Collaboration, Git, Photoshop, Blender
- Languages: Arabic (Native), English (Intermediate), French (Intermediate)
- Awards/Activities: Participant at AiHackTunisia (2018), Winner at 1337 Game Jam (2019),
 Participant at Google for MENA Summit (2019)